Hello everyone, my name is Daniel Yu, this is lecture 21, and in this presentation we'll
안녕하세요 여러분, 제 이름은 Daniel Yu입니다. 21번째 강의입니다. 이번 프레젠테이션에서는
talk about large language models and tool augmentation.
대규모 언어 모델과 도구 확장에 대해 이야기합니다.
So to give us a little bit of motivation, we've seen that large language models excel at natural
그래서 우리에게 약간의 동기를 부여하기 위해 우리는 대규모 언어 모델이 자연어 처리에 탁월하다는 것을 보았습니다.
language tasks, but language models also show that they have many inherent limitations.
그러나 언어 모델은 또한 많은 본질적인 한계가 있음을 보여줍니다.
So first of all, because LLMs are trained with corpus of texts relevant up to a certain time,
먼저, LLM은 특정 시점까지의 관련 텍스트 코퍼스로 훈련을 받았기 때문에
there are no access to up-to-date information. There are also many research that shows that
최신 정보에 접근할 수 없습니다. 또한 이를 보여주는 많은 연구 결과가 있습니다.
large language models are prone to fat hallucinations. They are also very bad at multi-step
큰 언어 모델은 뚱뚱한 환각을 일으키기 쉽습니다. 그들은 또한 다단계에 매우 나쁘다
reasoning, and they lack mathematical skills for precise calculations. Moreover, they are
추론 능력이 부족하고 정확한 계산을 위한 수학적 능력이 부족합니다. 게다가 그들은
unaware of the progression of time, so they are incapable of working with time-sensitive tasks.
시간의 진행을 인식하지 못하므로 시간에 민감한 작업을 수행할 수 없습니다.
Now, of course, some of these limitations might be partially solved by scaling up the model further,
물론 이러한 제한 사항 중 일부는 모델을 더욱 확장하여 부분적으로 해결될 수 있습니다.
but a much simpler solution and a much more popular solution is to overcome LLM limitations
하지만 훨씬 더 간단하고 훨씬 더 대중적인 솔루션은 LLM의 한계를 극복하는 것입니다.
with the use of external tools. External tools in this case refers to limited use tools such as
외부 도구를 사용하여. 이 경우 외부 도구는 다음과 같이 제한된 사용 도구를 나타냅니다.
calculators, calendar, or even the program interpreter. It can also include a search engine
계산기, 달력, 심지어 프로그램 통역사까지. 검색 엔진도 포함될 수 있습니다.
API, or an external database for expert knowledge, and they can be used for retrieval.
전문 지식을 위한 API 또는 외부 데이터베이스를 검색할 수 있습니다.
Now, in the modern days, we have the convenience of accessing these tools
이제 현대에는 이러한 도구에 편리하게 액세스할 수 있습니다.
with data frameworks such as LamaIndex. LamaIndex provides the interface between LLMs
LamaIndex와 같은 데이터 프레임워크를 사용합니다. LamaIndex는 LLM 간의 인터페이스를 제공합니다
and external tools or documents. In this case, LLM index actually has an indexing function
외부 도구 또는 문서. 이 경우 LLM 인덱스에는 실제로 인덱싱 기능이 있습니다.
that allows us to easily retrieve documents or APIs from external libraries. It has features
이를 통해 외부 라이브러리에서 문서나 API를 쉽게 검색할 수 있습니다. 특징이 있습니다
that allows us to access structured databases or unstructured documents such as raw files,
이를 통해 구조화된 데이터베이스나 원시 파일과 같은 구조화되지 않은 문서에 액세스할 수 있습니다.
or maybe semi-structured databases such as vector stores, or programmatic data such as application
또는 벡터 저장소와 같은 반구조화된 데이터베이스 또는 애플리케이션과 같은 프로그래밍 데이터일 수도 있습니다.
APIs. And for the outline of this presentation, we will cover six research papers. I will be
아피스. 그리고 이 프레젠테이션의 개요를 위해 우리는 6개의 연구 논문을 다룰 것입니다. 나는 될 것이다
covering the first three, two former art and agent bench, and Mohamed will be covering the last three.
처음 세 개, 전직 아트 및 에이전트 벤치 두 개를 다루고 Mohamed가 마지막 세 개를 다룰 예정입니다.
And these six papers all refers to the approaches that we can use fine-tune
그리고 이 6개 논문은 모두 우리가 미세 조정을 사용할 수 있는 접근 방식을 나타냅니다.
prompt or benchmark large language model augmented with external tools.
외부 도구로 강화된 대규모 언어 모델을 프롬프트하거나 벤치마킹합니다.
The first paper we talk about is ToolFormer. It is one of the first papers that discusses fine-tuning
우리가 이야기하는 첫 번째 논문은 ToolFormer입니다. 미세 조정을 논의한 최초의 논문 중 하나입니다.
model with the use of tools. To begin, the standard approach of tool use is using specific tools for
도구를 사용하여 모델을 만듭니다. 우선, 도구 사용의 표준 접근 방식은 특정 도구를 사용하는 것입니다.
specialized language model. But usually, this approach requires providing large amounts of
특수 언어 모델. 그러나 일반적으로 이 접근 방식은 많은 양의 정보를 제공해야 합니다.
demonstration of tool use, or we can use only a limited amount of tools for a domain-specific
도구 사용을 시연하거나 특정 도메인에 대해 제한된 양의 도구만 사용할 수 있습니다.
language model. Now, obviously, these types of tool use come with the issues of having high costs
언어 모델. 이제 분명히 이러한 유형의 도구 사용에는 높은 비용 문제가 발생합니다.
for large amounts of human annotations. If we use only a restricted amount of tools, then the large
대량의 인간 주석의 경우. 제한된 양의 도구만 사용한다면,
language model lacks generality. And in this case, prompts needs to be tailored to specific task or
언어 모델에는 일반성이 부족합니다. 그리고 이 경우 프롬프트는 특정 작업에 맞게 조정되어야 합니다.
specific tools. To solve this issue, the authors of this paper developed the methods of ToolFormer.
특정 도구. 이 문제를 해결하기 위해 본 논문의 저자는 ToolFormer의 방법을 개발했습니다.
First of all, ToolFormer gives models the ability to use APIs that have access to external database.
우선 ToolFormer는 외부 데이터베이스에 액세스할 수 있는 API를 사용할 수 있는 기능을 모델에 제공합니다.
But more importantly, ToolFormer is a methods of fine-tuning language models so that the model
그러나 더 중요한 것은 ToolFormer가 언어 모델을 미세 조정하는 방법이라는 것입니다.
itself can decide whether it will use a specific tools and when and how to use the available tools.
자체적으로 특정 도구를 사용할지 여부와 사용 가능한 도구를 언제, 어떻게 사용할지 결정할 수 있습니다.
Now, this is beneficial for the large language model because not only the large language models
이제 이는 대규모 언어 모델뿐만 아니라 대규모 언어 모델에도 도움이 됩니다.
has more tools to use, it's also because human intuition may not always be correct.
사용할 수 있는 도구가 더 많아졌지만 인간의 직관이 항상 정확하지는 않을 수도 있기 때문입니다.
And the tools that humans find useful in a particular scenario may not be the tool that the
그리고 인간이 특정 시나리오에서 유용하다고 생각하는 도구는 사용자가 사용하는 도구가 아닐 수도 있습니다.
model finds useful. Therefore, in ToolFormer, the use of tools should be learned in a self-supervised
모델이 유용하다고 생각합니다. 따라서 ToolFormer에서는 도구 사용법을 자기주도적으로 학습해야 합니다.
manner with our large amounts of human annotations showing it what to do. The approach of ToolFormer
무엇을 해야 할지 보여주는 대량의 인간 주석을 사용하는 방식입니다. ToolFormer의 접근 방식
should also not hurt the model's core language ability.
또한 모델의 핵심 언어 능력을 손상시키지 않아야 합니다.
For the approach of ToolFormer, let's say we want to equip a language model M with the ability to use
ToolFormer의 접근 방식을 위해 언어 모델 M에 다음을 사용할 수 있는 기능을 갖추려고 한다고 가정해 보겠습니다.
different tools from API costs. The idea here is that with just a handful of human examples of how the
API 비용과 다른 도구. 여기서 아이디어는 인간이 어떻게 행동하는지에 대한 소수의 예를 통해
APIs can be used, we can use in-context learning to let the language model M generalize and
API를 사용할 수 있고 상황 내 학습을 사용하여 언어 모델 M을 일반화하고
annotate a large dataset with the potential use of API costs. And then we can determine which
API 비용을 사용할 가능성이 있는 대규모 데이터 세트에 주석을 답니다. 그런 다음 우리는 어느 것을 결정할 수 있습니다
of these API costs actually will help the model predict future tokens and then fine-tune a model
이러한 API 비용 중 실제로는 모델이 미래 토큰을 예측하고 모델을 미세 조정하는 데 도움이 됩니다.
on the API costs for which it finds useful. So in this particular case, API call is represented
유용하다고 판단되는 API 비용에 대해 따라서 이 특별한 경우에는 API 호출이 표시됩니다.
by a pairs, C, which is AC, IC. And AC is the name of the API and IC is the input to the API.
쌍으로 C는 AC, IC입니다. AC는 API의 이름이고 IC는 API에 대한 입력입니다.
Now, inputs and outputs of API calls are represented as linearized text sequence,
이제 API 호출의 입력과 출력은 선형화된 텍스트 시퀀스로 표시됩니다.
EC or ECR. If the API call generator responds, the response has to be a single text sequence,
EC 또는 ECR. API 호출 생성기가 응답하는 경우 응답은 단일 텍스트 시퀀스여야 합니다.
and the response will be concatenated into the text sequence. And in this text sequence,
응답은 텍스트 시퀀스로 연결됩니다. 그리고 이 텍스트 시퀀스에서는
API, the NAPI, and the maps to symbols are all just special tokens.
API, NAPI 및 기호 매핑은 모두 특수 토큰일 뿐입니다.
Now, in order to augment a plaintext dataset, let's say we're given a plaintext dataset C and
이제 일반 텍스트 데이터세트를 확장하기 위해 일반 텍스트 데이터세트 C가 주어졌다고 가정해 보겠습니다.
we try to augment it to C star with API costs, we can do the following. First, we use a large
API 비용으로 이를 C 스타로 늘리려고 하면 다음을 수행할 수 있습니다. 먼저 우리는 큰 것을 사용합니다.
language model M to sample a large amount of potential API costs. Then we execute these API
대량의 잠재적 API 비용을 샘플링하기 위한 언어 모델 M. 그런 다음 이 API를 실행합니다.
costs and filter out the result that doesn't help the language model to predict future tokens.
비용을 절감하고 언어 모델이 미래 토큰을 예측하는 데 도움이 되지 않는 결과를 필터링합니다.
And finally, we merge the API costs that remains for different types of tools.
마지막으로 다양한 유형의 도구에 남아 있는 API 비용을 병합합니다.
Here is an example of the filtering process. So let's say we start with an example in the dataset
다음은 필터링 프로세스의 예입니다. 그럼 데이터 세트의 예부터 시작한다고 가정해 보겠습니다.
where the text is Pittsburgh is known as the Still City. This is the original text in the dataset.
텍스트가 피츠버그인 곳은 스틸 시티(Still City)로 알려져 있습니다. 이는 데이터 세트의 원본 텍스트입니다.
And from here, we ask the language model to sample a bunch of API costs that may potentially help
그리고 여기에서 언어 모델에 잠재적으로 도움이 될 수 있는 여러 API 비용을 샘플링하도록 요청합니다.
the language model to generate the centers. So here they samples a bunch of questions that they can
센터를 생성하는 언어 모델. 여기 그들은 그들이 할 수 있는 많은 질문의 샘플을 보여줍니다.
use in a question and answering API. And then we execute all these API costs to get an actual answer.
질문 및 답변 API에 사용합니다. 그런 다음 실제 답변을 얻기 위해 이러한 모든 API 비용을 실행합니다.
Then we check the loss function related to the API called plaintext. And we use some
그런 다음 plaintext라는 API와 관련된 손실 함수를 확인합니다. 그리고 우리는 일부를 사용합니다
self-supervised criterion to check whether we actually want to keep this API costs by whether
실제로 이 API 비용을 유지하고 싶은지 여부를 확인하는 자체 감독 기준
it's helpful for the language model to generate this text. And then for the API costs that remains,
언어 모델이 이 텍스트를 생성하는 데 도움이 됩니다. 그리고 남은 API 비용에 대해서는
we will see we will augment the linearized text sequence of API costs into the original text
API 비용의 선형화된 텍스트 시퀀스를 원본 텍스트로 확대하는 방법을 살펴보겠습니다.
and therefore augmenting this example.
따라서 이 예를 보강합니다.
Now to be specific, for each API, we write a prompt PX that encourages the language model
이제 구체적으로 말하자면, 각 API에 대해 언어 모델을 장려하는 프롬프트 PX를 작성합니다.
to annotate an example X with API costs. This example on the right is one of such prompts
API 비용으로 예시 X에 주석을 추가합니다. 오른쪽의 예는 그러한 프롬프트 중 하나입니다.
where you have a bunch of examples demonstration in the beginning. And then we just concatenate X
처음에는 많은 예제 데모가 있습니다. 그런 다음 X를 연결하면 됩니다.
as an input to the prompt. Now, given this, we will sample K candidates positions for doing API
프롬프트에 대한 입력으로. 이제 이를 고려하여 API 수행을 위한 K개의 후보자 위치를 샘플링하겠습니다.
costs by computing the probability that the next token is the special API token. That's why we
다음 토큰이 특수 API 토큰일 확률을 계산하여 비용을 계산합니다. 그렇기 때문에 우리는
computed this probability PI for a particular position I in the text example. And then let's say
텍스트 예제의 특정 위치 I에 대해 이 확률 PI를 계산했습니다. 그리고 말하자
we're given a sampling threshold tau. This is a positive number. And then we keep all positions
샘플링 임계값 tau가 제공됩니다. 이는 양수입니다. 그리고 우리는 모든 위치를 유지
I for which the probability of generating an API token is greater than the threshold.
API 토큰을 생성할 확률이 임계값보다 큰 I입니다.
This I is the set of candidate positions for API costs. Therefore, for every I as a candidate
이것이 I가 API 비용에 대한 후보 위치 집합입니다. 그러므로 나는 후보자로서 모든 사람에 대해
position, we'll sample up to M API costs, see a C1 I all the way to CMI. These API costs are
위치에 따라 최대 M API 비용까지 샘플링하고 C1 I부터 CMI까지 확인합니다. 이러한 API 비용은
generated by the original language model M. Now, after we execute all the sample API costs,
원본 언어 모델 M에 의해 생성되었습니다. 이제 모든 샘플 API 비용을 실행한 후,
we want to filter out API costs that do not provide benefits or provide more harm than benefits
혜택을 제공하지 않거나 혜택보다 해로움이 더 많은 API 비용을 필터링하고 싶습니다.
to generation. The way we do that is that we will define a self supervised loss Li of Z.
세대에. 이를 수행하는 방법은 Z의 자체 감독 손실 Li를 정의하는 것입니다.
Here, Z is just the linearized sequence of API costs. So this probability refers to the
여기서 Z는 API 비용의 선형화된 순서입니다. 따라서 이 확률은
probability of generating XJ, given the original prefix X1 to J minus one, and then a potential
J에서 1을 뺀 원래 접두사 X1이 주어지면 XJ를 생성할 확률, 그리고 잠재적인
API called Z. Now, let's say we're given a sequence of weights. This Li of Z computes the weighted
Z라는 API. 이제 일련의 가중치가 주어졌다고 가정해 보겠습니다. 이 Li of Z는 가중치를 계산합니다.
cross entropy loss for M. And for the weight function, authors of this paper use this weight
M에 대한 교차 엔트로피 손실. 그리고 가중치 함수의 경우 이 논문의 저자는 이 가중치를 사용합니다.
function. This is a piecewise linear function. But more importantly is that WT, the mass of the WTs
기능. 이는 조각별 선형 함수입니다. 그러나 더 중요한 것은 WT, 즉 WT의 질량입니다.
are more concentrated when T is close to zero. And it would just decrease when T gets further away.
T가 0에 가까울수록 더 집중됩니다. 그리고 T가 더 멀어지면 감소할 것입니다.
In fact, when T is five, this function will be zero. This ensures that the API costs happen
실제로 T가 5일 때 이 함수는 0이 됩니다. 이렇게 하면 API 비용이 발생합니다.
close to where the API outputs is actually helpful for generation.
API 출력이 실제로 생성에 도움이 되는 위치에 가깝습니다.
Now, in order to filter the API costs, we calculate the weighted loss of having
이제 API 비용을 필터링하기 위해 보유 손실의 가중 손실을 계산합니다.
and not having the results of API costs prefix. One of the things we calculate is
API 비용 결과가 접두사로 표시되지 않습니다. 우리가 계산하는 것 중 하나는
L plus i. This is just a loss when we include a particular sample API costs.
L 플러스 i. 특정 샘플 API 비용을 포함하면 이는 손실일 뿐입니다.
L minus i is calculated as the minimum of the loss of epsilon and the loss of
L 마이너스 i는 엡실론 손실과 의 손실의 최소값으로 계산됩니다.
using CI API call, but returning epsilon result. Here epsilon is just the empty string.
CI API 호출을 사용하지만 엡실론 결과를 반환합니다. 여기서 엡실론은 단지 빈 문자열입니다.
So these two compares the loss of the model when you include a sample API cost or when
따라서 이 두 가지는 샘플 API 비용을 포함할 때 또는
it does not include a sample API cost. Now, given a filtering threshold tau of F,
샘플 API 비용은 포함되지 않습니다. 이제 F의 필터링 임계값 tau가 주어지면,
we only keep API costs that reduce the loss by at least the threshold.
우리는 최소한 한도만큼 손실을 줄이는 API 비용만 유지합니다.
After filtering, we merge the remaining API costs and interleave them with the original
필터링 후 나머지 API 비용을 병합하여 원본과 인터리브합니다.
inputs. So you can see that from the examples on the right. When you make sure that an API cost
입력. 따라서 오른쪽의 예를 통해 이를 확인할 수 있습니다. API 비용이 확인되면
will be helpful for generation, you would augment by inserting them into the original text.
생성에 도움이 될 경우 원본 텍스트에 삽입하여 보강할 수 있습니다.
And with this method, we have made the data set C star that is augmented with API costs.
그리고 이 방법을 사용하여 API 비용이 증가하는 데이터 세트 C 스타를 만들었습니다.
The final step is to fine tune the language model M with the augmented data set C star.
마지막 단계는 증강 데이터 세트 C star를 사용하여 언어 모델 M을 미세 조정하는 것입니다.
Doing this will allow the additional API costs inserted help M predict future tokens.
이렇게 하면 삽입된 추가 API 비용이 M이 미래 토큰을 예측하는 데 도움이 됩니다.
Now, for inference, whenever it encounters the maps to function, it will
이제 추론을 위해 기능할 맵을 만날 때마다
indicates that it expects some response from the API costs. Therefore, the LLM pauses generation,
API 비용의 일부 응답이 예상됨을 나타냅니다. 따라서 LLM은 생성을 일시 중지하고,
execute the appropriate API costs for a response, and then concatenate that response into the
응답에 대해 적절한 API 비용을 실행한 다음 해당 응답을
generation, and then continue decoding with the generated response.
그런 다음 생성된 응답으로 디코딩을 계속합니다.
This is the approach and or say the constructions of two former.
이것이 접근 방식이며 두 가지 전자의 구성을 말합니다.
Now, the authors of this paper has done a few experiments in order to benchmark the effectiveness
이제 이 논문의 저자는 효율성을 벤치마킹하기 위해 몇 가지 실험을 수행했습니다.
of this approach. In order to do that, they explored the following five tools in an attempt to
이 접근 방식의. 이를 위해 그들은 다음과 같은 다섯 가지 도구를 탐색했습니다.
address the different shortcomings of language models. The first one is a question answering tool.
언어 모델의 다양한 단점을 해결합니다. 첫 번째는 질문 답변 도구입니다.
This is given by a secondary language model Atlas, which is a retrieval augmented generated
이는 검색 증강 생성인 보조 언어 모델인 Atlas에 의해 제공됩니다.
model that is used to answer simple factual questions. And then the second tool is Wikipedia
간단한 사실 질문에 답하는 데 사용되는 모델입니다. 두 번째 도구는 Wikipedia입니다.
search. This is an engine that when given a search term returns a short text snippet from Wikipedia.
찾다. 이것은 검색어가 주어지면 Wikipedia의 짧은 텍스트 조각을 반환하는 엔진입니다.
And then the calculator pretty straightforward is just perform simple arithmetic operation.
그리고 매우 간단한 계산기는 간단한 산술 연산을 수행하는 것입니다.
The calendar when given a when when we queried API with no inputs, it just returns the current date.
입력 없이 API를 쿼리하면 달력은 현재 날짜만 반환합니다.
And finally, the machine translation system is also given by a secondary language model.
그리고 마지막으로 기계 번역 시스템도 보조 언어 모델로 제공됩니다.
This is called an LLB. It's a 600 million parameter language model, and it can translate
이를 LLB라고 합니다. 6억 개의 매개변수 언어 모델이며 번역이 가능합니다.
from any of the 200 languages available back to English.
200개 언어 중 하나에서 영어까지 다시 사용할 수 있습니다.
For the experimental setup, we use a subsets of CC net as our large language modeling data set C.
실험 설정을 위해 CC net의 하위 집합을 대규모 언어 모델링 데이터 세트 C로 사용합니다.
And we use GPDJ as the language model M. In order to reduce computational cost to two former,
그리고 우리는 GPDJ를 언어 모델 M으로 사용합니다. 계산 비용을 전자 2개로 줄이기 위해,
we use some manual heuristics for some API to get a subsets of C.
우리는 C의 하위 집합을 얻기 위해 일부 API에 대해 수동 경험적 방법을 사용합니다.
For example, we will use calculator tools, if only let's say that there are three numbers in a window
예를 들어, 창에 세 개의 숫자가 있다고 가정하면 계산기 도구를 사용하겠습니다.
of 100 tokens. Otherwise, we will remove this tools from its use.
토큰 100개. 그렇지 않으면 이 도구를 사용하지 못하게 됩니다.
Also, in order to make sure models will call API tools more often during inference, we'll start an API call whenever API
또한 모델이 추론 중에 API 도구를 더 자주 호출하도록 하기 위해 API가 호출될 때마다 API 호출을 시작합니다.
token is one of the key most likely token. Now, here are the baseline model we compare with.
토큰은 가장 가능성이 높은 토큰 중 하나입니다. 이제 우리가 비교할 기본 모델이 있습니다.
First of all, GPDJ, which is the original base GPDJ model without fine tuning.
먼저, 미세 조정 없이 오리지널 베이스 GPDJ 모델인 GPDJ입니다.
GPDJ plus CC is GPDJ fine tuned on the subsets of CC net without any API calls.
GPDJ plus CC는 API 호출 없이 CC net의 하위 집합에서 미세 조정된 GPDJ입니다.
GPDJ fine tuned on the subsets of CC net without any API calls.
GPDJ는 API 호출 없이 CC 네트의 하위 집합을 미세 조정했습니다.
Two former is GPDJ fine tuned on the augmented data set C star.
두 번째는 증강 데이터 세트 C star에서 미세 조정된 GPDJ입니다.
And finally, two former disabled is GPDJ fine tuned on C star.
그리고 마지막으로 두 명의 이전 장애인이 C 스타에 대해 미세 조정된 GPDJ입니다.
But during inference, the API calls are disabled.
그러나 추론 중에는 API 호출이 비활성화됩니다.
This is done by manually setting the probability of the API token to zero.
이는 API 토큰의 확률을 0으로 수동으로 설정하여 수행됩니다.
Now, for the experiments on the benchmark, we use a bunch of downstream tasks and evaluate the
이제 벤치마크 실험을 위해 여러 다운스트림 작업을 사용하고
zero shot performance. The zero shot setting here is used because we don't want to tell
제로샷 성능. 여기서 제로 샷 설정은 알려주고 싶지 않기 때문에 사용됩니다.
the large language model which tools to use in events so that the language model can decide for
언어 모델이 결정할 수 있도록 이벤트에서 사용할 도구를 대규모 언어 모델
itself. The first set of benchmarks is Lama. This is originally used for mass language modeling.
그 자체. 첫 번째 벤치마크 세트는 Lama입니다. 이는 원래 대량 언어 모델링에 사용되었습니다.
And in the data set squad, Google RE and REX, the task here is to complete
그리고 데이터 세트 팀인 Google RE 및 REX에서 여기서 작업은 완료하는 것입니다.
short statement with missing facts. Now, two former here is prevented from using Wikipedia
사실이 누락된 짧은 진술. 이제 여기 전 두 사람은 위키피디아를 사용할 수 없습니다.
search APIs because a lot of the statements in these data sets are obtained directly from Wikipedia.
검색 API가 필요한 이유는 이러한 데이터 세트의 많은 내용이 Wikipedia에서 직접 얻은 것이기 때문입니다.
But even in this case, two former still outperform the baseline models.
그러나 이 경우에도 전자 두 개는 여전히 기본 모델보다 성능이 뛰어납니다.
As you can see from the table and the underlined accuracies.
표와 밑줄 친 정확도에서 볼 수 있듯이.
Now, for the math data sets, we use the ASDIV, SV, AMP, and MAWPS. These are just all math
이제 수학 데이터 세트의 경우 ASDIV, SV, AMP 및 MAWPS를 사용합니다. 이것들은 모두 수학일 뿐이야
word problem. And again, we use a zero shot settings because we may not be necessarily using
단어 문제. 그리고 다시 한 번 말씀드리지만, 반드시 사용하지 않을 수도 있기 때문에 제로 샷 설정을 사용합니다.
only calculators for math word problem. We could be also, the language model may
수학 단어 문제를 위한 계산기만 있습니다. 우리도 그럴 수 있습니다. 언어 모델은
decide to use maybe a question answering API. Now, we allow the models to make API calls.
질문 응답 API를 사용하기로 결정했습니다. 이제 모델이 API를 호출할 수 있도록 허용합니다.
If we allow the models to make API calls, it more than doubles their performance. This means that
모델이 API 호출을 할 수 있도록 허용하면 성능이 두 배 이상 향상됩니다. 이는 다음을 의미합니다.
two former can really solve some of these problems related to accurate computation and reasoning.
두 전자는 정확한 계산 및 추론과 관련된 이러한 문제 중 일부를 실제로 해결할 수 있습니다.
And the next set of data sets we look at is web questions, natural questions, and trivial QA.
그리고 우리가 살펴보는 다음 데이터 세트는 웹 질문, 자연 질문, 사소한 QA입니다.
These contains common sense questions. We evaluate the performance by checking whether
여기에는 상식적인 질문이 포함되어 있습니다. 여부를 확인하여 성과를 평가합니다.
the first 20 words predicted by a model contains the correct answer. And in here,
모델이 예측한 처음 20개 단어에는 정답이 포함됩니다. 그리고 여기에서는,
the question answering API is disabled for two former. Because again, this using this API will be
이전 두 가지에 대해서는 질문 응답 API가 비활성화되었습니다. 다시 말하지만, 이 API를 사용하면
a very direct approach. And we want to test the language model's
매우 직접적인 접근 방식입니다. 그리고 우리는 언어 모델의
AMP's ability, not the ability of the secondary language model atlas.
2차 언어 모델 아틀라스의 능력이 아닌 AMP의 능력입니다.
This is its performance. As you can see, there are also slight increase
이것이 그 성능입니다. 보시다시피 약간의 증가도 있습니다
with two former on all three benchmarks. Oh, for a more challenging task, we will evaluate
세 가지 벤치마크 모두에서 전자 두 개가 포함되었습니다. 아, 좀 더 어려운 작업에 대해서는 평가해 보겠습니다.
multi-lingual QA data set. These data sets can take six languages, such as Spanish, German,
다국어 QA 데이터 세트. 이러한 데이터 세트는 스페인어, 독일어,
Hindi, Vietnamese, Chinese, and Arabic. We evaluate the two former and all baseline models
힌디어, 베트남어, 중국어, 아랍어. 우리는 두 가지 이전 모델과 모든 기본 모델을 평가합니다.
on this task, and evaluate the percentage of times the model's generation contains the correct
이 작업에 대해 모델 생성에 올바른 내용이 포함된 횟수의 비율을 평가하세요.
answer. Now, interesting phenomena happens in this table. Using API calls actually improve
답변. 이제 이 표에서는 흥미로운 현상이 발생합니다. API 호출을 사용하면 실제로 개선됩니다.
two former's performance, but two former doesn't consistently outperform the base GPTJ models.
전자 두 개는 성능이 우수하지만 전자 두 개는 기본 GPTJ 모델보다 일관되게 성능이 뛰어나지는 않습니다.
And one of the main reason or explanation is that fine-tuning on the subsets of CCNet
그리고 주된 이유 또는 설명 중 하나는 CCNet의 하위 집합에 대한 미세 조정입니다.
actually deteriorate performance. Now, we look at temporal data sets, such as
실제로 성능이 저하됩니다. 이제 다음과 같은 시간 데이터 세트를 살펴보겠습니다.
tempLama and data set. These are both data sets where the answer to the question changes with time.
tempLama 및 데이터 세트. 두 가지 모두 질문에 대한 답이 시간에 따라 변하는 데이터 세트입니다.
More specifically, tempLama, it contains questions about facts, such as who is the head
좀 더 구체적으로 tempLama는 누가 우두머리인지 등 사실에 대한 질문을 담고 있습니다.
of government in New York City. Day set data set, on the other hand,
뉴욕시 정부의. 반면, 요일 세트 데이터 세트는
contains questions regarding dates and duration, such as what day of the week it is 10 days ago.
10일 전이 무슨 요일인지 등 날짜와 기간에 관한 질문이 포함되어 있습니다.
So interestingly, both data set had improved performance with two former, but upon closer
흥미롭게도 두 데이터 세트 모두 이전 두 데이터 세트에서 성능이 향상되었지만 더 가까워지면
evaluation, tempLama's increase in performance is not attributed to the calendar, is actually
평가 결과, tempLama의 성능 향상은 달력에 의한 것이 아니라 실제로는
attributed to Wikipedia search plus QA, because of how the information of time is related to
시간 정보가 어떻게 관련되어 있는지에 따라 Wikipedia 검색과 QA에 귀속됩니다.
facts about the common world. On the other hand, there is a significant improvements in day set,
일반적인 세계에 관한 사실. 반면에 요일 설정이 크게 개선되었습니다.
and this is attributed to the use of calendar tools.
이는 달력 도구를 사용했기 때문입니다.
We also wanted to see whether fine-tuning on two former actually deteriorates the language
우리는 또한 이전 두 가지를 미세 조정하면 실제로 언어가 저하되는지 확인하고 싶었습니다.
original, the language model's original language ability. Therefore, there has been an experiment
원본, 언어 모델의 원래 언어 능력입니다. 그래서 실험이 있었습니다
made that compares the proplexity of different base models on wiki text and another subsets
위키 텍스트와 다른 하위 집합에 대한 다양한 기본 모델의 복잡성을 비교하도록 만들어졌습니다.
of ccinet that is different from the subset that was originally used for the fine-tuning.
원래 미세 조정에 사용된 하위 집합과 다른 ccinet의 집합입니다.
So we want to ensure that the language model's performance does not deteriorate,
그래서 우리는 언어 모델의 성능이 저하되지 않도록 하고 싶습니다.
and as you can see from the table, proplexity doesn't change that much.
표에서 볼 수 있듯이, 복잡성은 그다지 변하지 않습니다.
And finally, there are experiments that test how the performance scales with the size of the
마지막으로 성능이 크기에 따라 어떻게 확장되는지 테스트하는 실험이 있습니다.
language model. So for this experiment, we have used the same experimental setup for
언어 모델. 따라서 이 실험에서는 동일한 실험 설정을 사용했습니다.
different parameter models in the GPT-2 family. And if you compare the curve of two former and
GPT-2 제품군의 다양한 매개변수 모델. 그리고 이전과 이전의 두 곡선을 비교해 보면
two former disabled in the below three diagram, we see that the ability to use tool only emerges
아래 세 다이어그램에서 이전 두 개가 비활성화되어 도구를 사용할 수 있는 기능만 나타나는 것을 알 수 있습니다.
at around 775 million parameter models. So this is it about two former, and next we will talk about
약 7억 7,500만 개의 매개변수 모델이 있습니다. 이것이 이전의 두 가지에 관한 것입니다. 다음은 다음에 대해 이야기하겠습니다.
art, which stands for automatic reasoning and to use.
자동 추론과 사용을 의미하는 예술.
For the motivation of art, we've seen that in context learning allows large language models
예술의 동기를 위해 우리는 맥락 학습에서 대규모 언어 모델이 가능하다는 것을 확인했습니다.
to quickly adapt to new tasks using natural language instructions and a few demonstrations.
자연어 지침과 몇 가지 데모를 사용하여 새로운 작업에 빠르게 적응합니다.
However, there are also severe performance limitations around multi-step reasoning,
그러나 다단계 추론에는 심각한 성능 제한이 있습니다.
mathematical problem solving, and other complex tasks.
수학적 문제 해결 및 기타 복잡한 작업.
While there are variants of prompting methods such as auto-ching of thought and least to most
생각의 자동 칭과 같은 다양한 프롬프트 방법이 있지만 대부분의 경우
prompting that we've seen, these can mitigate issues involving multi-step reasoning. But for
우리가 본 것처럼 이는 다단계 추론과 관련된 문제를 완화할 수 있습니다. 이 아니라면
this presentation, we try to incorporate the use of tools into the model. That's why we introduce
이번 프레젠테이션에서는 도구 사용을 모델에 통합하려고 합니다. 그렇기 때문에 소개합니다
art, which is a framework that try to resolve the issue by automatically generate
art는 자동으로 생성하여 문제를 해결하려고 하는 프레임워크입니다.
decompositions of intermediate reasoning steps for instances of new tasks. While it automatically
새로운 작업의 인스턴스에 대한 중간 추론 단계의 분해. 하면서 자동으로
use the appropriate tools at each of the intermediate steps.
각 중간 단계에서 적절한 도구를 사용하십시오.
In the art framework, we provide the large language models with demonstrations of how
아트 프레임워크에서 우리는 대규모 언어 모델에 방법을 보여주는 데모를 제공합니다.
to decompose several related tasks and how to use any tools from a tool library. We will see later
여러 관련 작업과 도구 라이브러리의 도구를 사용하는 방법을 분해합니다. 나중에 보자
that the composition of tasks and the related tasks are given by a structured query language
작업 및 관련 작업의 구성이 구조화된 쿼리 언어에 의해 제공된다는 것
so that we can use it to parse intermediate steps. But overall, art is a framework that encourages
이를 사용하여 중간 단계를 구문 분석할 수 있습니다. 그러나 전반적으로 예술은 다음을 장려하는 프레임워크입니다.
the model to generalize decomposed new tasks, select and use tools. On the right hand side,
분해된 새로운 작업을 일반화하고, 도구를 선택하고 사용하는 모델입니다. 오른쪽에는
we can see examples of such a process. And at the end of the stage, we can also see that
우리는 그러한 과정의 예를 볼 수 있습니다. 그리고 무대가 끝나면 우리는 그것을 볼 수 있습니다
if there is a mistake in the decomposition of reasoning, it also allows the user to fix any
추론 분해에 실수가 있는 경우 사용자가 이를 수정할 수도 있습니다.
mistakes by adding new tools or updating the task library. We'll see more about this later.
새 도구를 추가하거나 태스크 라이브러리를 업데이트하여 실수를 저지르십시오. 이에 대해서는 나중에 더 자세히 살펴보겠습니다.
Okay, so art is actually a framework that builds on both the idea of chain of thought and auto
좋아요, 예술은 사실 사고의 사슬과 자동차라는 아이디어를 바탕으로 구축된 프레임워크입니다.
chain of thought. If you don't know auto chain of thought, it's like chain of thought. But the
생각의 사슬. 생각의 자동 연쇄를 모르면 생각의 연쇄와 같습니다. 하지만
demonstrations are automatically constructed by the large language model by sampling different
데모는 다양한 샘플링을 통해 대규모 언어 모델에 의해 자동으로 구성됩니다.
questions and generating their respective reasoning chain and use them as an example.
질문을 던지고 각각의 추론 체인을 생성하여 예시로 사용합니다.
Art has the advantage that it enables cross task demonstration and it improves
예술은 교차 작업 시연이 가능하고 향상된다는 장점이 있습니다.
accuracies of intermediate reasoning steps. Art doesn't require any additional training
중간 추론 단계의 정확성. 예술에는 추가 교육이 필요하지 않습니다.
or two specific prompts. User can replace the underlying large language model or add new tools
또는 두 개의 특정 프롬프트. 사용자는 기본 대규모 언어 모델을 교체하거나 새 도구를 추가할 수 있습니다.
if they find useful. On the right is a table of what kind of feature each of these tools or
유용하다고 판단되면. 오른쪽에는 각 도구 또는 기능의 종류에 대한 표가 있습니다.
approach uses. As you can see, COT has multi step reasoning as a feature. And then auto COT
접근 방식을 사용합니다. 보시다시피 COT에는 다단계 추론 기능이 있습니다. 그리고 자동 COT
uses less supervision because it generates its demonstration automatically. Two former
데모를 자동으로 생성하므로 감독이 덜 필요합니다. 두 전
enables the use of tool and art claims to have all six features.
6가지 기능을 모두 갖춘 도구 및 예술 주장을 사용할 수 있습니다.
Now we take a look at an overview of this framework in its core. Art uses a frozen
이제 우리는 이 프레임워크의 핵심 개요를 살펴보겠습니다. 예술은 냉동을 사용합니다
large language model to decompose instances of a new task into multiple steps without supervision.
감독 없이 새로운 작업의 인스턴스를 여러 단계로 분해하는 대규모 언어 모델입니다.
In the first stage, we will do prompt building. So in prompt building, art retrieves similar task
첫 번째 단계에서는 신속한 구축을 수행합니다. 따라서 신속한 구축에서 예술은 유사한 작업을 검색합니다.
from a task library and adds instances of those tasks as demonstration in the prompt.
작업 라이브러리에서 해당 작업의 인스턴스를 프롬프트에 데모로 추가합니다.
A demonstration in a task library is written in a custom format. This custom format is called
태스크 라이브러리의 데모는 사용자 정의 형식으로 작성됩니다. 이 사용자 정의 형식을
parsing expression in grammar. This grammar helps break down every task instance into a sequence of
문법 표현을 파싱합니다. 이 문법은 모든 작업 인스턴스를 일련의 작업으로 분류하는 데 도움이 됩니다.
sub steps. Some of these sub steps contain symbols corresponding to the use of tools.
하위 단계. 이러한 하위 단계 중 일부에는 도구 사용에 해당하는 기호가 포함되어 있습니다.
In this paper, the author also refers to the compositions as programs. This is because
본 논문에서 저자는 작곡을 프로그램이라고도 부른다. 이 때문입니다
sequential reasoning steps and symbolic calls are a resemblance to conventional programs with
순차적 추론 단계와 기호 호출은 기존 프로그램과 유사합니다.
function costs. The next stage is generation. During generation time, the large language
기능 비용. 다음 단계는 세대이다. 세대 시간 동안 큰 언어는
model writes its own program. And art will pause this generation if it encounters a tool call
모델은 자체 프로그램을 작성합니다. 그리고 예술은 도구 호출이 발생하면 이 세대를 일시 중지합니다.
in the generated text. It calls the tool, integrates the tools output back to the program,
생성된 텍스트에서 도구를 호출하고 도구 출력을 다시 프로그램에 통합합니다.
and the LLM continues to coding. The final optional stage is for human feedback,
LLM은 코딩을 계속합니다. 마지막 선택 단계는 사람의 피드백을 위한 것입니다.
which humans can find any mistakes or error within the reasoning steps and then adds the
인간은 추론 단계에서 실수나 오류를 발견하고 이를 추가할 수 있습니다.
composition demonstration to the task library or edit the tools in the tool library in order to
작업 라이브러리에 구성 데모를 표시하거나 도구 라이브러리에서 도구를 편집하여
fix them and improve performance on a particular task of interest.
문제를 수정하고 관심 있는 특정 작업의 성능을 향상시킵니다.
Here is an example of everything we talked about in the previous outline.
다음은 이전 개요에서 이야기한 모든 내용의 예입니다.
On the left hand side, this shows a few examples of tasks from the task library.
왼쪽에는 태스크 라이브러리의 태스크에 대한 몇 가지 예가 표시됩니다.
These examples or these tasks will be used for the LLM for potential cross-task generalization
이러한 예 또는 이러한 작업은 잠재적인 교차 작업 일반화를 위해 LLM에 사용됩니다.
of the compositions. This example is an arithmetic question, and it shows
작곡의. 이 예는 산술 문제이며 다음을 보여줍니다.
how to generate a decomposition to solve a calculation of questions like this. The bottom
이와 같은 질문의 계산을 해결하기 위해 분해를 생성하는 방법. 바닥
example is a task from the anachromism. It means that to check whether objects or events
예는 아나크로미즘의 과제입니다. 사물이나 사건을 확인한다는 뜻이다.
happen in their respective era. On the right hand side is an example of a task from the
각자의 시대에 일어난다. 오른쪽에는 작업의 예가 있습니다.
physics question answering dataset. It asks for a classical mechanic questions, and the LLM here
물리학 질문 답변 데이터 세트. 고전적인 기계공학에 대한 질문을 하고 여기서 LLM을 묻습니다.
decomposes the questions by first using a search engine to find the appropriate physical formula,
먼저 검색 엔진을 사용하여 적절한 물리적 공식을 찾아 질문을 분해하고,
and then it asks a code generation tools to generate the code to execute this formula.
그런 다음 코드 생성 도구에 이 수식을 실행하기 위한 코드를 생성하도록 요청합니다.
Finally, a Python program to substitute the correct parameters and answer the questions
마지막으로 올바른 매개변수를 대체하고 질문에 답하는 Python 프로그램입니다.
in the end. In the task library of art, it has programs for a small seed set of tasks from Big
결국. 예술 작업 라이브러리에는 Big의 작은 작업 세트에 대한 프로그램이 있습니다.
Bench. Big Bench is a benchmark that measures the capabilities and limitations of language model.
벤치. Big Bench는 언어 모델의 기능과 한계를 측정하는 벤치마크입니다.
It contains problems such as traditional natural language processing problems, mathematics,
전통적인 자연어 처리 문제, 수학,
common sense reasoning, and questions answering. In order to evaluate these benchmarks,
상식 추론, 질문 답변. 이러한 벤치마크를 평가하기 위해,
we grouped the five most used skills in this benchmark. The first one being arithmetic,
우리는 이 벤치마크에서 가장 많이 사용되는 5가지 기술을 그룹화했습니다. 첫 번째는 산술이고,
which is simply solving algebra problems, code generations, and the skill to execute
이는 단순히 대수 문제, 코드 생성 및 실행 기술을 해결하는 것입니다.
mostly Python program. The next skill is search and question decomposition.
주로 Python 프로그램입니다. 다음 기술은 검색 및 질문 분해입니다.
Then we have freeform reasoning, which is to explain step-by-step reasoning in natural language.
그런 다음 자연어로 추론을 단계별로 설명하는 자유 형식 추론이 있습니다.
Finally, we have string operation, which is the skill of reformatting and editing strings and more.
마지막으로 문자열 작업, 즉 문자열 형식을 다시 지정하고 편집하는 기술 등이 있습니다.
In the task library, we select two to four tasks from every group. There was a total of 15 tasks
작업 라이브러리에서는 모든 그룹에서 2~4개의 작업을 선택합니다. 총 15개의 과제가 있었습니다
chosen by these five groups. We write a program for, let's say, a few examples from each task.
이 다섯 그룹이 선택했습니다. 예를 들어 각 작업의 몇 가지 예를 위한 프로그램을 작성합니다.
The program includes the potential cause to external tools.
프로그램에는 외부 도구에 대한 잠재적인 원인이 포함되어 있습니다.
Now we talk about parsing expression grammar. This is a custom query language used to represent
이제 표현식 문법을 구문 분석하는 방법에 대해 이야기합니다. 이는 표현하는 데 사용되는 사용자 정의 쿼리 언어입니다.
the decomposed reasoning steps and trying to incorporate function calls to external tools.
분해된 추론 단계와 외부 도구에 대한 함수 호출을 통합하려고 시도합니다.
Each of the program consists of a series of nodes. The first node is always an input node.
각 프로그램은 일련의 노드로 구성됩니다. 첫 번째 노드는 항상 입력 노드입니다.
The input node contains the task name, the instruction describing a task,
입력 노드에는 작업 이름, 작업을 설명하는 명령,
and input for a particular instance of the task. Input node is then followed by a bunch of
작업의 특정 인스턴스에 대한 입력입니다. 그런 다음 입력 노드 뒤에는 여러 개의 노드가 옵니다.
sub-step nodes. Sub-step nodes are all labeled by query answer pairs, such as these.
하위 단계 노드. 하위 단계 노드는 모두 다음과 같은 쿼리 응답 쌍으로 레이블이 지정됩니다.
In a query answer pair, the query entries contain, first of all, the name of the task,
쿼리 응답 쌍에서 쿼리 항목에는 우선 작업 이름,
and then it was followed by the input to the task. The answer entry, AI, contains either the
그런 다음 작업에 대한 입력이 이어졌습니다. 답변 항목인 AI에는 다음 중 하나가 포함됩니다.
generated output given by the task or the result of using external tools.
작업에 의해 생성된 출력 또는 외부 도구를 사용한 결과입니다.
The program then ends with a dummy sub-task, where the query is just a special symbol end of query,
그런 다음 프로그램은 더미 하위 작업으로 끝납니다. 여기서 쿼리는 쿼리의 특수 기호 끝입니다.
and the answer field contains the final answer.
답변 필드에는 최종 답변이 포함됩니다.
For task retrieval, let's say we're given a new task.
작업 검색을 위해 새로운 작업이 주어졌다고 가정해 보겠습니다.
Art then retrieves a number of tasks from the task library
그런 다음 Art는 작업 라이브러리에서 여러 작업을 검색합니다.
to construct a dynamic multitask prompt that was used for demonstrations.
데모에 사용된 동적 멀티태스킹 프롬프트를 구성합니다.
Now, from here, the paper explored two strategies on how to retrieve similar tasks.
이제 여기에서 논문은 유사한 작업을 검색하는 방법에 대한 두 가지 전략을 탐색했습니다.
The first strategy is task cluster-based. This will work when there are a lot of labeled
첫 번째 전략은 작업 클러스터 기반입니다. 이 방법은 라벨이 많이 붙은 경우에 작동합니다.
examples on a new task. So what it does is it iterates over all five groups and select a field
새로운 작업에 대한 예. 따라서 수행하는 작업은 5개 그룹 모두에 대해 반복하고 필드를 선택하는 것입니다.
task program from each group to compose the prompt. Then the task cluster with the highest
각 그룹의 작업 프로그램을 사용하여 프롬프트를 구성합니다. 그런 다음 가장 높은 작업 클러스터
performance on the labeled example is chosen. The second approach is LLM similarity-based.
레이블이 지정된 예의 성능이 선택됩니다. 두 번째 접근 방식은 LLM 유사성 기반입니다.
This approach is a little bit more involved. What it does is it crafts a field-shot prompt
이 접근 방식은 조금 더 복잡합니다. 그것이 하는 일은 현장 촬영 프롬프트를 만드는 것입니다.
with task pairs between each group of skills. Each task includes a name, an instruction,
각 기술 그룹 간의 작업 쌍이 있습니다. 각 작업에는 이름, 지침,
and a few IO examples. Then for every pair, we use the in-contact learning abilities of LLM to
그리고 몇 가지 IO 예시입니다. 그런 다음 모든 쌍에 대해 LLM의 접촉 학습 기능을 사용하여
provide labels of either similar or not-similars. Now, at runtime, what we'll do is we have the
유사하거나 유사하지 않은 라벨을 제공합니다. 이제 런타임에 우리가 할 일은
test task and we pair it with every task in the task library. Then utilizing the in-contact
테스트 작업을 수행하고 이를 작업 라이브러리의 모든 작업과 연결합니다. 그러면 인택트를 활용해서
learning ability of the original LLM, we want the LLM to also apply labels of similar and not
원래 LLM의 학습 능력을 고려하여 LLM이 유사한 라벨을 적용하고 그렇지 않은 라벨도 적용하기를 원합니다.
similar to these new pairs of tasks. Then we will rank on the probabilities of having
이러한 새로운 작업 쌍과 유사합니다. 그럼 확률에 따라 순위를 매겨보겠습니다.
similar label and choose the highest ranked task in order to be used inside the prompts of the new
비슷한 라벨을 선택하고 새 프롬프트 내에서 사용하려면 가장 높은 순위의 작업을 선택하세요.
tasks. In the R2 library, we remark that in the parsing expression grammar, if a task name
작업. R2 라이브러리에서는 구문 분석 표현식 문법에서 작업 이름이
matches the name of a tool, we will incorporate the result of this external tool in this intermediate
도구 이름과 일치하면 이 외부 도구의 결과를 이 중간 단계에 통합합니다.
steps. For example, in this paper, the two libraries are seeded with the following example tools.
단계. 예를 들어, 이 문서에서는 두 라이브러리에 다음 예제 도구가 포함되어 있습니다.
The first one is a search tool. This tool uses the SERP API and it provides an API for
첫 번째는 검색 도구입니다. 이 도구는 SERP API를 사용하며 다음에 대한 API를 제공합니다.
Google search. The corresponding query entry has a task name given by search and then the
구글 검색. 해당 쿼리 항목에는 검색을 통해 제공된 작업 이름이 있고
arguments is the search query. In the code generation tool, we use the codex model. The
인수는 검색어입니다. 코드 생성 도구에서는 코덱스 모델을 사용합니다. 그만큼
corresponding entry is a task name is generate Python code and then the argument is a generation
해당 항목은 작업 이름이고 Python 코드 생성이고 인수는 생성입니다.
instruction written in natural language. The third tool is code execution where we run Python code in
자연어로 작성된 지시. 세 번째 도구는 Python 코드를 실행하는 코드 실행입니다.
a virtual environment. This virtual environment will have arithmetic symbolic and scientific
가상 환경. 이 가상 환경은 산술 기호 및 과학 기능을 갖습니다.
computing package already pre-installed. The query will have code execute as its task name and then
컴퓨팅 패키지가 이미 사전 설치되어 있습니다. 쿼리는 작업 이름으로 코드를 실행한 다음
the body of the code as its argument or in most cases, the body of the code will be just the answer
코드 본문을 인수로 사용하거나 대부분의 경우 코드 본문이 답일 뿐입니다.
will be just the result of the code generation tool.
코드 생성 도구의 결과일 뿐입니다.
Finally, we talk about the stage where it's optional for human to provide feedback
마지막으로 인간이 피드백을 제공하는 것이 선택 사항인 단계에 대해 이야기합니다.
to the reasoning traces and the outputs of art. Well, first of all, since art does not require
추론의 흔적과 예술의 결과물에. 글쎄요, 우선 예술은 필요하지 않기 때문에
additional fine-tuning, user can incorporate feedback into the framework by editing the task or the
추가적인 미세 조정을 통해 사용자는 작업이나 작업을 편집하여 프레임워크에 피드백을 통합할 수 있습니다.
tool library. The diagram here shows an example where the user corrects a specific program by
도구 라이브러리. 여기 다이어그램은 사용자가 특정 프로그램을 수정하는 예를 보여줍니다.
including additional steps and then adding this program to the task library. In part A, users
추가 단계를 포함시킨 다음 이 프로그램을 태스크 라이브러리에 추가합니다. 파트 A에서는 사용자
edit the program by adding two sub steps. The first step is to round the answer to the nearest
두 개의 하위 단계를 추가하여 프로그램을 편집합니다. 첫 번째 단계는 답을 가장 가까운 값으로 반올림하는 것입니다.
integer and then we add a unit of measurement to the answer. This corrects or refined the answer to
정수를 선택하고 답에 측정 단위를 추가합니다. 이는 다음에 대한 답변을 수정하거나 개선합니다.
the questions. Part B, the user implements a tool for lookup of common words in the dictionaries.
질문. 파트 B에서는 사용자가 사전에서 일반적인 단어를 검색하는 도구를 구현합니다.
And here in these examples, the user interferes with the compositions of tasks,
그리고 여기 이 예에서는 사용자가 작업 구성을 방해합니다.
but the generation performed at the generation performed at every step is still performed by
그러나 모든 단계에서 수행된 생성에서 수행된 생성은 여전히 ​​에 의해 수행됩니다.
the large language models. In this example, human feedbacks are seen as a form of debugging
대규모 언어 모델. 이 예에서는 인간의 피드백이 디버깅의 한 형태로 간주됩니다.
where user edit the programs instead of creating the programs. Also because human expert knowledge
여기서 사용자는 프로그램을 생성하는 대신 프로그램을 편집합니다. 또한 인간의 전문지식이 있기 때문에
are used, these simple operations can very easily improve the performance on the target task.
이러한 간단한 작업을 사용하면 대상 작업의 성능을 매우 쉽게 향상시킬 수 있습니다.
Now, in order to test the performance of art, here we have the experimental setup,
이제 예술의 성능을 테스트하기 위해 여기에 실험 설정이 있습니다.
in which case in addition to the 15 tasks from the task library, we also evaluate art
이 경우 작업 라이브러리의 15개 작업 외에도 아트도 평가합니다.
on 19 additional tasks from the big bench benchmark. We also evaluate art on the MMLU
빅벤치 벤치마크의 19개 추가 작업에 대해 알아보세요. 우리는 또한 MMLU의 예술을 평가합니다.
benchmark. Here MMLU refers to massive multitask language understanding. And we further evaluate
기준. 여기서 MMLU는 대규모 멀티태스킹 언어 이해를 의미합니다. 그리고 우리는 추가로 평가합니다.
a subset of tasks used in two former. This help us compare the approaches using tools
이전 두 가지 작업에서 사용된 작업의 하위 집합입니다. 이는 도구를 사용하여 접근 방식을 비교하는 데 도움이 됩니다.
with fine tuning versus in-contact learning. The first in LLMU uses a struct GPT and the
미세 조정과 접촉 학습을 통해. LLMU의 첫 번째는 구조체 GPT를 사용하고
cogeneration tool is OpenAI codecs. Here in the examples, we use two demonstration programs
열병합 발전 도구는 OpenAI 코덱입니다. 여기 예제에서는 두 가지 데모 프로그램을 사용합니다.
from each task, and we will report the performance average over five runs.
각 작업에서 5회 실행에 대한 성능 평균을 보고합니다.
Here we also introduce some baseline approach for this experiment.
여기서는 이 실험에 대한 몇 가지 기본 접근 방식도 소개합니다.
In the few shot baseline, we will just prompt the LLM with input output pairs with no intermediate
몇 번의 샷 기준선에서는 중간 없이 입력 출력 쌍으로 LLM에 메시지를 표시합니다.
steps. And we will use three to five examples depending on which benchmark is being used.
단계. 그리고 어떤 벤치마크가 사용되는지에 따라 3~5개의 예를 사용하겠습니다.
Auto chain of thought is also compared, which auto chain of thought automatically generate
생각의 자동 연쇄도 비교되는데, 자동으로 생성되는 생각의 자동 연쇄
multi-step reasoning in natural language. This baseline doesn't include the user tools.
자연어의 다단계 추론. 이 기준에는 사용자 도구가 포함되지 않습니다.
Then there is art tool. This is art, but the tool library is turned off. So it should be art minus
다음은 미술 도구입니다. 이것은 예술이지만 도구 라이브러리가 꺼져 있습니다. 그럼 예술 마이너스가 되어야지
two here. And finally GPT-3 best, which shows the result of the best published GPT-3 and codecs
여기 두 개. 그리고 마지막으로 가장 잘 게시된 GPT-3 및 코덱의 결과를 보여주는 GPT-3 best입니다.
with multi-step decomposition and tool use. Here the compositions are given by a few
다단계 분해 및 도구 사용. 여기에 구성은 몇 가지에 의해 제공됩니다
additional human supervision. Here is the results on art and all the baseline models
추가적인 인간 감독. 예술과 모든 기본 모델에 대한 결과는 다음과 같습니다.
on the task library. As you can see on the right hand side, the five color coded groups
작업 라이브러리에 있습니다. 오른쪽에서 볼 수 있듯이 다섯 가지 색상으로 구분된 그룹은
refers to the five skills and tasks within each of these skills.
5가지 기술과 각 기술 내의 과제를 나타냅니다.
As we can see, because art uses the task library, it should naturally perform well,
보시다시피 아트는 태스크 라이브러리를 사용하기 때문에 자연스럽게 잘 수행되어야 합니다.
and as we can see in this table that they do. And these delta with art rows actually
그리고 이 표에서 볼 수 있듯이 그들은 그렇게 합니다. 그리고 아트 행이 있는 이러한 델타는 실제로
shows us some of the improvements of accuracies when using art compared with other baseline models.
다른 기본 모델과 비교하여 아트를 사용할 때 정확도가 일부 향상되었음을 보여줍니다.
Here are the results on the big bench task. And these are the similar groupings of tasks
다음은 빅 벤치 작업에 대한 결과입니다. 그리고 이것들은 유사한 작업 그룹입니다.
into five categories of skills. Here are the results on the MMLU task. And this time the task
5가지 스킬 카테고리로 나뉜다. MMLU 작업의 결과는 다음과 같습니다. 그리고 이번에는 과제
only contains two groups of skills, but it still has a pretty straightforward increase in performance.
두 가지 기술 그룹만 포함되어 있지만 여전히 성능이 매우 간단하게 향상됩니다.
Here we also evaluate the performance on additional benchmarks. First of all, here we have
여기서는 추가 벤치마크에 대한 성능도 평가합니다. 우선, 여기에는
the performance of art compared to two former. As we can see on most of the benchmarks,
이전 두 사람과 비교하여 예술의 성과. 대부분의 벤치마크에서 볼 수 있듯이
art has an improved accuracy. Although the comparison here is not really exact because
예술의 정확도가 향상되었습니다. 여기에서의 비교는 실제로 정확하지는 않지만
two former uses a smaller GBTJ model and art here uses a more performant frozen LN.
두 전자는 더 작은 GBTJ 모델을 사용하고 여기서는 더 성능이 뛰어난 고정 LN을 사용합니다.
We also try to improve art with self-consistency. Here the self-consistency
우리는 또한 자기 일관성을 가지고 예술을 향상시키기 위해 노력합니다. 여기서 자기 일관성
is the majority vote over 15 generations. And as we can see, although not too much
15세대에 걸친 다수결이다. 보시다시피 너무 많지는 않지만
self-consistency does improve the performance of art by a little over all these potential tasks.
자기 일관성은 이러한 모든 잠재적인 작업에 비해 예술의 성능을 약간 향상시킵니다.
Finally, the author also examined adding human feedback to both
마지막으로 저자는 두 가지 모두에 인간 피드백을 추가하는 방법도 검토했습니다.
chain of thought style reasoning and art reasoning. In both cases, editing the program leads to a
사고방식 추론과 예술 추론의 사슬. 두 경우 모두 프로그램을 편집하면
significant gains in task performance, which is expected because it has human determinations.
인간의 결단력이 있기 때문에 작업 성능이 크게 향상될 것으로 예상됩니다.
On the right hand side, we show some examples of corrected error. Here, I think one of the
오른쪽에는 수정된 오류의 몇 가지 예가 나와 있습니다. 여기서 제 생각에는 다음 중 하나가 될 것 같습니다.
authors just randomly select five instances of the model generator program that gives an error
저자는 오류를 발생시키는 모델 생성기 프로그램의 5개 인스턴스를 무작위로 선택했습니다.
and then correct them respectively. Here, C is just a correct errors in a sub step. A means
그런 다음 각각 수정합니다. 여기서 C는 하위 단계의 올바른 오류일 뿐입니다. 수단
adding missing sub steps and T is just defined a new tool or new demonstrations as a feedback.
누락된 하위 단계를 추가하면 T는 피드백으로 새 도구나 새 데모로 정의됩니다.
Okay, this concludes the art paper. And finally, for the next paper, we will take a bit of a detour
자, 이것으로 아트페이퍼를 마칩니다. 그리고 마지막으로, 다음 논문에서는 조금 우회하겠습니다.
and consider large language model as an agent. And we'll see that these agent will requires
대규모 언어 모델을 에이전트로 간주합니다. 그리고 우리는 이 에이전트가 다음을 요구한다는 것을 알게 될 것입니다.
the use of two as an ability. Because LLMs can do more than natural language tasks,
두 가지를 능력으로 사용합니다. LLM은 자연어 작업 이상의 일을 할 수 있기 때문에
they are also capable of making decisions and executing instructions.
그들은 또한 결정을 내리고 지시를 실행할 수도 있습니다.
Thus, there has been an urgent need to evaluate LLMs as agents in an interactive environment.
따라서 대화형 환경에서 LLM을 에이전트로 평가하는 것이 시급히 필요했습니다.
Most of the agent benchmarks on LLMs focus on just a single environment. And there has been a
LLM에 대한 대부분의 에이전트 벤치마크는 단일 환경에만 중점을 둡니다. 그리고 거기에는
lack of systematic and standard benchmark to reflect the abilities of LLMs as an agent
에이전트로서 LLM의 능력을 반영하는 체계적이고 표준적인 벤치마크가 부족함
in most practical use cases. Therefore, the authors of this paper proposed agent bench
대부분의 실제 사용 사례에서. 따라서 본 논문의 저자는 에이전트 벤치를 제안했습니다.
as a comprehensive benchmark that evaluates LLMs as agents across eight different environments.
8개의 서로 다른 환경에서 LLM을 에이전트로 평가하는 포괄적인 벤치마크입니다.
Although many improved strategies are proposed, this paper evaluates LLMs with the most
많은 개선된 전략이 제안되었지만 본 논문에서는 LLM을 가장 많이 평가합니다.
primitive chain of thought prompting. Because chain of thought is easiest, it's cheapest,
원시적인 사고 사슬을 자극합니다. 생각의 연쇄가 가장 쉽기 때문에 가장 저렴하고,
and it's also the most common way for people to deploy LLMs as an agent. This paper also offered
이는 또한 사람들이 LLM을 에이전트로 배포하는 가장 일반적인 방법이기도 합니다. 이 논문은 또한 제공
an integrated toolkits that enable customization of the of the benchmarks for model assessments.
모델 평가를 위한 벤치마크의 사용자 정의를 가능하게 하는 통합 툴킷입니다.
This toolkit is currently openly available to the research community.
이 툴킷은 현재 연구 커뮤니티에서 공개적으로 사용할 수 있습니다.
Now, to look at the eight different environments within agent bench, we will note that these
이제 에이전트 벤치 내의 8가지 서로 다른 환경을 살펴보기 위해 다음 사항에 주목하겠습니다.
environments are categorized by three types of grounding, a code game and web.
환경은 코드 게임과 웹이라는 세 가지 유형의 접지로 분류됩니다.
First of all, we look at the code grounded environment. Now, since LLMs can generate
먼저 코드 기반 환경을 살펴보겠습니다. 이제 LLM이 생성할 수 있으므로
high quality code, we want to evaluate their ability to assist human interaction with computer
고품질 코드를 사용하여 인간과 컴퓨터의 상호 작용을 지원하는 능력을 평가하고 싶습니다.
interface. The first of these benchmark is the operating system benchmark. So now we're given
상호 작용. 이러한 벤치마크 중 첫 번째는 운영 체제 벤치마크입니다. 이제 우리에게 주어진 것은
an LLM the ability to access and manipulate operating system in a virtual machines terminal.
LLM은 가상 머신 터미널에서 운영 체제에 액세스하고 조작하는 기능입니다.
The LLM will be given a task such as find the total numbers of files inside a particular
LLM에는 특정 파일 내의 총 파일 수를 찾는 것과 같은 작업이 제공됩니다.
directory. Then the LLM will generate text based instructions. For this particular case,
예배 규칙서. 그런 다음 LLM은 텍스트 기반 지침을 생성합니다. 이 특별한 경우에는
it will be any valid batch commands to interact with the system. And the final observation will
시스템과 상호 작용하는 데 유효한 배치 명령이 될 것입니다. 그리고 마지막 관찰은
be the system standard output. So for this task, we use a success rate as the performance metric.
시스템 표준 출력이 됩니다. 따라서 이 작업에서는 성공률을 성능 지표로 사용합니다.
We also have the database environment, which examines LLM's ability to operate and
우리는 또한 LLM의 운영 능력을 검사하고
examine real databases via SQL. In here, for example, there will be LLM will be given a task
SQL을 통해 실제 데이터베이스를 검사합니다. 예를 들어 여기에서는 LLM에게 작업이 주어집니다.
such as what was the total numbers of metals won by the United States when it was given a table
예를 들어, 테이블이 주어졌을 때 미국이 획득한 금속의 총 개수는 얼마입니까?
of Olympic medal counts. Then the LLM will generate SQL commands in order to get the final result.
올림픽 메달 집계. 그런 다음 LLM은 최종 결과를 얻기 위해 SQL 명령을 생성합니다.
We also had a knowledge graph environment. The problem here is to require the agent to
지식 그래프 환경도 있었습니다. 여기서 문제는 에이전트에게 다음을 요구하는 것입니다.
make decision with incomplete information and manage uncertainty. Because the LLMs can only
불완전한 정보로 의사결정을 내리고 불확실성을 관리합니다. LLM은 오직
operate on a partial subset of these graphs. Therefore, it tests the language model's ability
이 그래프의 부분적인 하위 집합에서 작동합니다. 따라서 언어 모델의 능력을 테스트합니다.
for planning and to using such as interacting with the knowledge graph interface. For knowledge
지식 그래프 인터페이스와의 상호 작용 등 계획 및 사용을 위해. 지식을 위해
graph reasoning, we will adopt the F1 square theorem. The next grounding we look at is the
그래프 추론에서는 F1 제곱 정리를 채택하겠습니다. 다음으로 살펴볼 접지는
game grounded environment. Here we will evaluate the agent's ability to design strategies for
게임 기반 환경. 여기서는 에이전트의 전략 설계 능력을 평가하겠습니다.
playing game, make reasonable choices and follow instructions. Here the fourth environment, it's
게임을 하면서 합리적인 선택을 하고 지시를 따르세요. 여기 네 번째 환경이 있습니다.
digital card games. In digital card games, there will be like a lot of cards and there will be an
디지털 카드 게임. 디지털 카드 게임에는 많은 카드가 있고
abundant text description of cards. So the model need to utilize this context and we will evaluate
카드에 대한 풍부한 텍스트 설명. 따라서 모델은 이러한 맥락을 활용해야 하며 우리는 평가할 것입니다.
the model's ability to understand game rules, operate and evaluate its ability to make strategic
게임 규칙을 이해하고, 전략을 수립하는 능력을 운영하고 평가하는 모델의 능력
decisions. The next game environment is lateral thinking puzzle. This task evaluates the LLMs
결정. 다음 게임 환경은 측면적 사고 퍼즐입니다. 이 작업은 LLM을 평가합니다.
ability to deduce facts from unconventional perspective and explore new ideas. So in particular,
관습에 얽매이지 않는 관점에서 사실을 추론하고 새로운 아이디어를 탐구하는 능력. 그래서 특히,
in lateral thinking puzzle, there will be a host giving an obscure description of a scene,
측면적 사고 퍼즐에는 진행자가 장면에 대해 모호하게 설명하고,
such as a man slipped with the lights off and next morning he suicides after opening windows.
예를 들어, 불이 꺼진 채 미끄러졌다가 다음날 아침 창문을 열고 자살한 남자 등이 있습니다.
And why is that? Then the LLM agent will try to ask questions with binary answers such as did he
왜 그런데? 그런 다음 LLM 에이전트는 다음과 같은 이진 답변으로 질문을 시도합니다.
suicide out of guilt or are the windows he opened in the room he slips in? Well, the host will then
죄책감으로 자살한 걸까요, 아니면 그가 들어간 방의 창문이 열린 걸까요? 그럼 호스트는 그럼
answer yes, no or irrelevant and with this information, the LLMs tries to discover the
예, 아니오 또는 관련이 없다고 대답하고 이 정보를 사용하여 LLM은
true plot under this obscure description. Now to evaluate the performance, the true plot is divided
이 모호한 설명 아래의 실제 플롯입니다. 이제 성능을 평가하기 위해 실제 플롯을 나눕니다.
into several bullet points and the performance of LLM is evaluated by the progress of the game.
몇 가지 주요 항목으로 구분되며 LLM의 성능은 게임 진행에 따라 평가됩니다.
Next environment is householding. This benchmark takes place in ALF world. This is an interactive
다음 환경은 집안일이다. 이 벤치마크는 ALF 세계에서 이루어집니다. 이것은 대화식입니다
environment taking place inside a household and it's completely text based instructions.
가정 내에서 발생하는 환경에 대한 설명이며 완전히 텍스트 기반 지침입니다.
So for example, we will ask the LLM to perform tasks like clean some soap bar and put it on a
예를 들어, 우리는 LLM에게 비누를 청소하고 비누를 욕조 위에 놓는 것과 같은 작업을 수행하도록 요청할 것입니다.
countertop. Then the LLM will generate a sequence of text instructions guiding an agent to navigate
수조. 그런 다음 LLM은 상담원이 탐색할 수 있도록 안내하는 일련의 텍스트 지침을 생성합니다.
the household and perform the following jobs. The performance of this in the performance is evaluated
가구를 관리하고 다음 작업을 수행합니다. 이번 공연에서는 그 성능이 평가된다.
by success rate. The next, the final grounding is the web grounded environment where we evaluate
성공률로. 다음으로 최종 접지는 우리가 평가하는 웹 기반 환경입니다.
an LLM's ability to navigate through web pages. Task in this categories will be presented with a
웹 페이지를 탐색하는 LLM의 능력. 이 카테고리의 작업은
GUI web page, but because LLMs are text based, they will be given HTML elements. So the available
GUI 웹 페이지이지만 LLM은 텍스트 기반이므로 HTML 요소가 제공됩니다. 그래서 사용 가능한
actions of an LLM in these tasks will be to choose one of the HTML elements in the web page,
이러한 작업에서 LLM의 작업은 웹 페이지의 HTML 요소 중 하나를 선택하는 것입니다.
click or type a word, search an answer and select a certain options. The two task here is web shopping
단어를 클릭하거나 입력하고, 답변을 검색하고, 특정 옵션을 선택하세요. 여기서 두 가지 작업은 웹 쇼핑입니다.
which the task is to look for a particular product with a particular description and the
특정 설명이 포함된 특정 제품을 찾는 작업입니다.
objective is to go to a web page with this product. And finally, the web browsing task
목표는 이 제품이 포함된 웹페이지로 이동하는 것입니다. 그리고 마지막으로 웹 브라우징 작업입니다.
is to navigate web pages with a particular objectives.
특정 목표를 가지고 웹페이지를 탐색하는 것입니다.
Now in order to test all these benchmarks, the author evaluate 27 API based LLMs and open source
이제 이러한 모든 벤치마크를 테스트하기 위해 저자는 27개의 API 기반 LLM 및 오픈 소스를 평가합니다.
LLMs with these benchmarks. The interaction history between LLMs and the environment are
이러한 벤치마크를 갖춘 LLM. LLM과 환경 간의 상호 작용 기록은 다음과 같습니다.
given as prompts. Here is a table of scores achieved across all benchmarks and all LLMs.
프롬프트로 제공됩니다. 다음은 모든 벤치마크와 모든 LLM에서 얻은 점수 표입니다.
You can see that on some of these challenging benchmarks, top language models are capable
이러한 까다로운 벤치마크 중 일부에서 최고의 언어 모델이 가능하다는 것을 알 수 있습니다.
of dealing with real world interactions. For example, GPT-4 has the best performance
실제 세계의 상호작용을 다루는 것입니다. 예를 들어 GPT-4의 성능이 가장 좋습니다.
out of with six of the eighths of the datasets in Agent Bench. Following GPT-4,
Agent Bench의 데이터 세트 중 8분의 6 중 6개입니다. GPT-4에 이어,
Claude2, Claude and GPT-3.5 Turbo has also decent scores. Other API based LLMs will have poor
Claude2, Claude 및 GPT-3.5 Turbo도 괜찮은 점수를 받았습니다. 다른 API 기반 LLM은 품질이 좋지 않습니다.
performance, but most of them can solve quite a few percent of problems within each of the
성능을 발휘하지만 대부분은 각 영역 내에서 꽤 몇 퍼센트의 문제를 해결할 수 있습니다.
environment. Open source LLMs on the other hand, commonly fails to solve some of the problems
환경. 반면 오픈 소스 LLM은 일반적으로 일부 문제를 해결하지 못합니다.
such as knowledge graph. Most of them were failing the task. Digital card game and also
지식 그래프와 같은 것입니다. 그들 대부분은 임무에 실패했습니다. 디지털 카드 게임 및
household problems they have difficulty with. This identify most open source language model as
그들이 어려움을 겪는 가정 문제. 이는 대부분의 오픈 소스 언어 모델을 다음과 같이 식별합니다.
to be incapable as being an agent in the real world environment.
실제 환경에서 에이전트가 될 수 없습니다.
And here are two more graphs representing the performance of LLMs across the 27 LLMs.
다음은 27개의 LLM에 대한 LLM의 성과를 나타내는 두 개의 그래프입니다.
And on the graph on the right hand side, it actually displays the overall scores of LLMs as
그리고 오른쪽 그래프에는 실제로 LLM의 전체 점수가 다음과 같이 표시됩니다.
agents in the Agent Bench benchmark. Now, to further identify the reasons of failures in some
Agent Bench 벤치마크의 에이전트. 이제 일부 실패의 원인을 더 자세히 파악하기 위해
of these LLMs, we categorize LLM agents finish reason into five different types. First of all,
이러한 LLM 중에서 우리는 LLM 상담원이 완료 이유를 5가지 유형으로 분류합니다. 가장 먼저,
if it's completed, it'll be written as completed. But there are also four failure reasons.
완료되면 완료로 기록됩니다. 하지만 실패 이유도 네 가지가 있습니다.
First of all, contact limit exceeded. It happens when the interaction history
우선 연락 한도를 초과했습니다. 상호작용 기록이 표시될 때 발생합니다.
exceeds the LLMs maximum context links. So the interaction history was too long
LLM의 최대 컨텍스트 링크를 초과합니다. 그래서 상호작용 기록이 너무 길었어요
to be used as an input. We also had invalid format. This happens when the agent
입력으로 사용됩니다. 형식도 잘못되었습니다. 상담원이 할 때 이런 일이 발생합니다.
don't follow the format instruction. Invalid action happens when it follows the format
형식 지침을 따르지 마십시오. 형식을 따르면 잘못된 작업이 발생합니다.
instructions, but the action it chosen is invalid. Finally, task limit exceeded happens when
지침이 있지만 선택한 작업이 잘못되었습니다. 마지막으로 작업 제한 초과는 다음과 같은 경우에 발생합니다.
an agent cannot solve a problem after a predefined finite amounts of maximum interactions.
에이전트는 미리 정의된 유한한 양의 최대 상호 작용 이후에는 문제를 해결할 수 없습니다.
This happened when the generation of the LLM gets inside an infinite loop. So it could happen
이는 LLM 생성이 무한 루프에 들어갈 때 발생했습니다. 그래서 그런 일이 일어날 수 있었어
when the agent keep repeating the same action that gets nowhere.
에이전트가 아무데도 도달하지 못하는 동일한 작업을 계속 반복하는 경우입니다.
And finally, here is a table showing the most common reasons for LLMs to fail across all
마지막으로 LLM이 모든 분야에서 실패하는 가장 일반적인 이유를 보여주는 표는 다음과 같습니다.
eight different environments. Most of the LLM agents fails to solve challenging tasks in a given
8개의 서로 다른 환경. 대부분의 LLM 에이전트는 주어진 상황에서 어려운 작업을 해결하지 못합니다.
time or falls into repeated generation. For example, in the knowledge graph benchmark and the
시간이 지나거나 반복세대에 빠지게 됩니다. 예를 들어, 지식 그래프 벤치마크와
lateral thinking puzzle benchmark, most many of the LLM fails because task limit exceeded.
측면적 사고 퍼즐 벤치마크에서 대부분의 LLM이 작업 제한을 초과하여 실패했습니다.
And for database and in a digital card game, many LLM fails because it provides instruction
데이터베이스와 디지털 카드 게임의 경우 많은 LLM이 지침을 제공하기 때문에 실패합니다.
with invalid format. Any LLMs that fails with invalid format or invalid action are usually
형식이 잘못되었습니다. 잘못된 형식이나 잘못된 작업으로 인해 실패하는 LLM은 일반적으로
caused by LLMs inability to follow instructions. And if LLM fails a lot with task limit exceeded,
LLM이 지침을 따르지 못해서 발생합니다. 그리고 작업 제한을 초과하여 LLM이 많이 실패하면
it indicates that the LLM has weak multi-term decision abilities.
이는 LLM의 다항적 결정 능력이 약하다는 것을 나타냅니다.
And this concludes the presentation of Agent Bench.
이것으로 Agent Bench의 프레젠테이션을 마칩니다.